<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Long Trail on Paul D&#39;Amora</title>
    <link>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The Long Trail on Paul D&#39;Amora</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Day Twenty</title>
      <link>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/daytwenty/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/daytwenty/</guid>
      <description>13.6 miles (275.7 total) Missing
Unfortunately my phone was bricked from water damage on Day Nineteen, so several of my journal entries were lost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day Nineteen</title>
      <link>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/daynineteen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/daynineteen/</guid>
      <description>19.7 miles (262.1 total) Missing
Unfortunately my phone was bricked from water damage on Day Nineteen, so several of my journal entries were lost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day Eighteen</title>
      <link>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/dayeighteen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/dayeighteen/</guid>
      <description>15.2 miles (242.4 total) Missing
Unfortunately my phone was bricked from water damage on Day Nineteen, so several of my journal entries were lost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day Seventeen</title>
      <link>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/dayseventeen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/dayseventeen/</guid>
      <description>17.8 miles (227.2 total) Missing
Unfortunately my phone was bricked from water damage on Day Nineteen, so several of my journal entries were lost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day Sixteen</title>
      <link>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/daysixteen/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/daysixteen/</guid>
      <description>8.5 miles (209.4 total) Missing
Unfortunately my phone was bricked from water damage on Day Nineteen, so several of my journal entries were lost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day Fifteen</title>
      <link>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/dayfifteen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/dayfifteen/</guid>
      <description>18.7 miles (200.9 total) My hard day yesterday didn&amp;rsquo;t leave me with a lot of energy for today. I didn&amp;rsquo;t leave camp until 10 and then I had an easy walk down to the road. I didn&amp;rsquo;t really enjoy the whole Winooski River section. It was tons of road walking and walking around farm land, which was pretty boring. Luckily I was able to move quickly which helped make up for my late start.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day Fourteen</title>
      <link>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/dayfourteen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/dayfourteen/</guid>
      <description>22.8 miles (182.2 total) Missing
Unfortunately my phone was bricked from water damage on Day Nineteen, so several of my journal entries were lost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day Thirteen</title>
      <link>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/daythirteen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/daythirteen/</guid>
      <description>4.6 miles (159.4 total) I didn&amp;rsquo;t get on the trail until much later than I had hoped today. I needed the extra rest though. When I got off yesterday, my feet were in pretty bad shape. Hopefully I can do a better job of keeping them dry now, but unfortunately the trail doesn&amp;rsquo;t make that easy. I got started at around 3:15 at Lincoln Gap and made great time to the summit of Mount Abraham.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day Twelve</title>
      <link>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/daytwelve/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/daytwelve/</guid>
      <description>5.1 miles (154.8 total) Today I only hiked the 5.1 miles to the Lincoln Gap. The trail wasn&amp;rsquo;t too hard, and there were lots of great views for such a short distance. I actually ended up running the last couple of miles (except for the rocky ledges) since it was mostly a gradual downhill dirt trail. I will be spending the night in Burlington with my girlfriend, and hopefully I will return to the trail tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day Eleven</title>
      <link>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/dayeleven/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/dayeleven/</guid>
      <description>16.6 miles (149.7 total) It&amp;rsquo;s 10 PM and I just spent an hour fixing my hammock setup in the dark without a headlamp (it broke). I&amp;rsquo;m not sure why I was having trouble tonight, but it put me in kind of a bad mood. Lots of good views today. The terrain is getting a little more difficult. I had a bad fall off of a slippery rock. 16.6 miles today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day Ten</title>
      <link>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/dayten/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/dayten/</guid>
      <description>12.9 miles (133.1 total) I almost quit today. I did not feel very well this morning and decided it would be better for me to just sleep. So I ended up not waking up until 12:30 and after a quick breakfast/lunch hit the trail at about 1:15. I had decided a few miles in that I wanted my girlfriend to come pick me up at Brandon Gap, because I felt very sick and just didn&amp;rsquo;t want to hike anymore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day Nine</title>
      <link>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/daynine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/daynine/</guid>
      <description>18.6 miles (120.2 total) Today was long. I got up and hit the trail by 7:15, and made it to the trailhead by 10:15. A very nice man picked me up and brought me in to town. HE told me all about his life; his health problems, his girlfriend, his kids. He told me he lives vicariously through people like me. It was surprising to see someone open up to me like that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day Eight</title>
      <link>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/dayeight/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/dayeight/</guid>
      <description>4.3 miles (101.6 total) Another late start today (maybe I should set an alarm). I didn&amp;rsquo;t leave camp until 10 AM, and then I slowly trudged up Killington Peak. It was super hot, and I was probably still a bit dehydrated from yesterday, so I didn&amp;rsquo;t get to the summit until 1 PM. It was an amazing view, despite all of the development. I had planned to spend the night in Rutland, but instead I decided to hang out in Killington all day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day Seven</title>
      <link>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/dayseven/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/dayseven/</guid>
      <description>19.8 miles (97.3 total) I didn&amp;rsquo;t feel nearly as good today as I did the day before. It was easy hiking, but I felt sluggish all day. I now realize it&amp;rsquo;s probably because I was adding Mio to my water all day, rather than drinking normal water. Oh well, rookie mistake. I got a nice surprise when I got to Clarendon Gorge. Alex and Taylor were waiting just before the bridge with trail magic!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day Six</title>
      <link>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/daysix/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/daysix/</guid>
      <description>17.8 miles (77.5 total) Today was a great day. I woke up at about 5:30 AM, heard rain, and decided to sleep a bit more. Well I didn&amp;rsquo;t end up leaving camp until 10:30, but by the time I got up, there was no more rain, and I felt great. The hike to the summit of Bromley didn&amp;rsquo;t take long, and there were some amazing views. I didn&amp;rsquo;t see any spots for a hammock, so it was probably good that I didn&amp;rsquo;t camp there the night before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day Five</title>
      <link>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/dayfive/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/dayfive/</guid>
      <description>2.0 miles (59.7 total) Amanda dropped me off at the Rt 11&amp;frasl;30 trailhead at about 6:30 PM today. I made great time to the Bromley shelter and got there just after 7. I started to continue on to the summit, but I realized I had forgotten to camel up on water, so I ended up staying at the Bromley shelter. Only 2 miles today, but I&amp;rsquo;m excited to get back to it tomorrow!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day Four*</title>
      <link>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/dayfourz/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/dayfourz/</guid>
      <description>0.0 miles (57.7 total) Unfortunately today I&amp;rsquo;m going to have to leave the trail for a couple of days. Alex and Taylor will also be leaving in order to sort out their resupplies and gear, while New Edition will be switching to section hiking. I&amp;rsquo;m already itching to get back out on the trail, but there are more important things than trail life at the moment.
Jeff dropped us off in town at a cute little restaurant this morning called Up For Breakfast, where we got breakfast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day Four</title>
      <link>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/dayfour/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/dayfour/</guid>
      <description>10.6 miles (57.7 total) Today wasn&amp;rsquo;t too bad for hiking. We only had to do an easy 10.6 miles to get to the VT 11&amp;frasl;30 trailhead. The whole way was VT flat, so it went quickly and I got to the trailhead at 1:15. Finding a hitch into town wasn&amp;rsquo;t too difficult (it only took about 5 minutes) and we ended up grabbing some food at a small bar called Firefly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day Three</title>
      <link>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/daythree/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/daythree/</guid>
      <description>19.1 miles (47.1 total) We got a decent start on our descent of Glastenbury mountain this morning. We made good time and got to Story Spring shelter by about noon, where we stopped for lunch. We caught up to Goose and Ribbet there and also met a guy named Bigfoot who&amp;rsquo;s trying to hike the entire AT in less than 100 days. Just before we got to the base of Stratton Mountain, Taylor started to feel nauseous, so New Addition (Rob) and myself went on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day Two</title>
      <link>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/daytwo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/daytwo/</guid>
      <description>14.7 miles (28.0 total) Double trail magic day! I left Congdon shelter at around 7 AM and I hiked most of the way to Rt. 9 with Alex and Taylor (whom I had met the night before). There was an awesome gentleman with trail magic in the Rt. 9 parking lot, which was awesome. Then, just a couple hundred feet after that trail head, there was more trail magic!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day One</title>
      <link>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/dayone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.pauldamora.com/trips/the-long-trail/dayone/</guid>
      <description>13.3 miles (13.3 total) I started off at around 9 AM at the Pine Cobble trail head. I made pretty good time up the trail &amp;ndash; the view from Pine Cobble was fantastic &amp;ndash; and I was at the Long Trail trail head by 11 AM. I ended up forgetting to bring toilet paper, so all I had was a couple of tissues I got from my dad&amp;rsquo;s car. We&amp;rsquo;re about to get a little graphic here, but I would have probably been okay, though unfortunately I was super sick to my stomach all day, and ended using all of the tissues as toilet paper today.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>